クッフフ… いとも簡単に毒は回った
I am Worm, a Shadow Beast.
今　確かに俺じゃなく 女のほうを狙った 殺すつもりで
Which group do you belong to? We're bodyguards for
the Nostrade Family. I see.
おい　近過ぎねえか？
After the Phantom Troupe's
raid on the auction, Uvogin has single-handedly
annihilated the Mafia pursuit.
大丈夫だ。
Now, they watch the arrival
この距離なら　ポットクリンは カウントを始めない。 問題は　王とプフ本体が 別行動をとり出した時。
of the secret weapon dispatched
by the Mafia's Ten Dons, the Shadow Beasts.
これは　通称「人ぶどう」です。
Man...
兵隊の素質ある者が ふ化を待っています。
Not one of them put up much of a fight. Uvo! Yeah?
急げ！　急げ！ 急げ！　急げ！　急げ！
Hey, don't interfere.
早く！　早く！ 急げ！　急げ！
Let Uvo handle it. Care for a round, Feitan?
急げ！　急げ！ 急げ！　急げ！　急げ！　早く！ こっちも急ぐぞ！ ウェルフィンはどこだ？
He's going to fight the
Shadow Beasts by himself?
ダメだな　バラバラ過ぎて
The Shadow Beasts, huh?
「リビング・デッド・ドールズ」は 使えない。
Where did you hide the merchandise?
キルア。
We killed them. So where's the merchandise?
王が宮殿正面口に来たわ。 ああ。
If you don't answer me...
今　ペイジンの隠れ家に入ったわ。 廊下を歩いてる。
That stung.
左目だけで見れば　その水晶には
Now you can't escape...
記憶された者の現在が映る。
Make your choice.
水晶には今　同時に
Do you want to die
underground, at my hands?
ゴンとピトー　キルアと私 プフと王とユピーが映ってる。
Or on the surface, at the
hands of the other three?
テレビ画面を 分割して見ている感じよ。 ただ　私が右目で見たのは
Idiot.
そして この能力で見えるのは　３人まで。
Here he goes. Uvo's getting serious... Four.
もし　右目だけでもう１人 誰かを見てしまったら　古い順
You're the one
まず　プフが見えなくなる。
who can't escape!
分身に惑わされないってこと。 本体がハエほどしかない時なら
Big Bang Impact:
Fist of Destruction
文字通り ひねりつぶせると思わない？ あっ。
I-I don't believe it!
分裂した時がプフを倒すチャンス。
I've never seen a Nen user
of this caliber before.
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ　ハァ。
That's...
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。
A spider tattoo.
Then he's...
進め。
He's just throwing a straight right,
with a little added Nen.
右手奥の扉だ。
Fool. Nice...
[TEL] [TEL]
I can even turn it into hard spikes, yup. You throw a strong punch, but it's meaningless if
you can't connect, yup.
ポケットに忍ばせたまま 携帯電話の声を拾うことは
They managed to damage
ピトーの聴覚をもってすれば 十分可能である
Uvogin's iron skin with nothing
but body hair and teeth. Must be skilled Nen users.
[TEL]　ピトー様　ウェルフィンです。
I'm impressed. Thirteen.
[TEL]　取り急ぎ用件のみ述べます。
No way!
[TEL]　私とブロヴーダとで 娘を奪い返しました。
Sorry.
[TEL]　賊がまだ 付近をうろついているので
Want a hand, Uvo? Keep out of this!
宮殿地下に　籠城しております。
Damn it... It's futile.
[TEL]　声をお聞かせします。
You can't shake off thousands of spikes
[TEL]　もスもス　ピトー様？
Then I'll use you as my fist!
[TEL]　コムギと申スます。 [TEL]　ワダす　無事ですんで 安心ください。
Since I can manipulate it at will, I can relax certain sections of
my body hair as necessary, yup.
分かった。 [TEL]　では。 [TEL]
We've got Muscles on the ropes. That's bull.
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。
Did it finally kick in? My fangs secrete a tranquilizer that's meant to instantly incapacitate you...
これで　いいですね？
Bastard...
はい。 できれば…　ハァ　ハァ…。
Everything from the neck up is unaffected, so you can still feel pain and fear. So sit back and enjoy.
医者をお願いします　プフ殿。
If he were using a lethal poison,
this fight would be over.
だよな？
I'm sure he likes to torture opponents.
自分以外の者での再構築も可能 顔　骨格　声帯さえも
I keep numerous leeches
of all sizes within me...
フフフフ… これでピトーもかかった 魔法に
They'll enter your body
through your wounds, and deposit their eggs in your bladder.
呪縛から解放される ウソという名の魔法
These spotted leeches are
a gift from me to you. You're totally disgusting!
さぁ　早く ゴンとピトーの続きを見るといい
Most people die from the
excruciating pain
さぁ　約束通り　カイトを治せ。
They're going to lose...
そうすれば こっちも　あのコを解放する。
The Shadow Beasts will lose.
名前…。
You can't bite me when I'm
all the way over here.
君は　僕のお願いを聞いてくれた。
A bullet?
だから　せめて 僕も君に正直でいようと思う。
No... It's a fragment of Leech's
skull that he bit off!
思い出した。
What if our eardrums had burst?
君は　あの時の…。
Sorry about that! But that would've given my plan away.
死人を生き返らせる ことはできなかった。
Wait, Kurapika!
僕の能力で　できたのは
What are you doing?
腐敗しないように つくり直すことと
Shouldn't that be obvious? I'm going to capture him.
操ることだけだった。
It's impossible! You saw what he's capable of! You're going to get yourself killed!
もう　元には戻せないんだ。
I hear tremendous rage and hatred.
ごめんね。
Kurapika!
それより　ゴンは？
Wild Flower. The perfect song to relax you.
えっ？　あっ…　あぁ　そうね。
Has everyone calmed down?
えっ？
Let's cool our heads, and devise a plan together.
どうした？
Y-Yeah...
そんな…　どういうこと!?
What kind of abilities do the
other members possess?
えっ？
I bet they're all ridiculously strong...
カイト…。
However, I still must capture them.
カイトが…
Leader, I can make this happen. What?
死んだ…。
Let me go.
) )
Bring the car, so we can
leave at a moment's notice. R-Right.
俺が…。
Shizuku!
Would you suck the poison and
leeches from my body? Your vacuum will do the trick.
((進む先 勝っても負けても地獄だぞ))
Blinky can suck out poison,
but nothing alive. What?
俺が行かなければ…。
Let me see.
カイトは　死ななかった。
This is a spotted leech... It takes one day to migrate to the bladder, before laying its eggs and dying.
俺が…　俺のせいで…。
However, they require a specific
ammonia level to hatch. If there isn't enough, the eggs don't hatch, and they
can be excreted harmlessly.
俺が…　のこのこ ついて行ったから…。
Make sure they're ice-cold! Don't get too greedy!
やっぱり…　俺が…。
Okay, get that poison out of me.
殺したのはピトーだ!! 俺じゃ　ない!!
Did you see that? Yeah.
でも…　俺が…。
Those chains came from nowhere,
to wrap around his body. Is it a new Shadow Beast?
俺が…　カイトを…。
Uvo can't move because of the tranquilizer, and the leeches are still inside him.
殺したのは　俺…。
Then that's that...
Let's go and save him. Good grief. He's so much trouble. I have a trace for now.
俺のせいで…。
I used In to conceal the thread.
違う!!　あいつだ!! でも　やっぱり　俺が…。
So as long as they don't use
Gyo to spot the needle, I can follow them anywhere. Okay, let's find them
before they notice it.
) ((あんな奴には 絶対…　絶対に負けない))
This is our chance to finish the
remaining Shadow Beasts. Franklin, we're counting on you
to bring back lots of beer.
カイトが死んだ… カイトが死んだ…。
Man, the chase sounds more fun... Let's go! Indeed.
カイトが死んだ！
The spiders...
助けて…。 誰か助けて！
We'd need all the remaining members
カイトが…　カイトが…。
just to stand a chance...
)
Understood.
もう　戻せない？
Chains...
俺のせいで…　誰がカイトを…。
Hey, driver...
カイトを助けて。 違う　違う　違う　違う　違う！
You think these chains can hold me?
でも　でも　でも　でも…
If you don't kill me now,
you'll regret it later. Shut up. Don't you understand? This is a golden opportunity.
あっ。
Kurapika, watch... Watch the road!
何だ？　助けてくれるのかな？
How can he be this strong? Even if my body weren't paralyzed,
I'd still be having trouble...
そうか　本当だ 死んでるなんて　ウソだ
He's put enough Nen into these chains
ちゃんと　治してくれるんだ あれ？
to keep a master Enhancer in check?
何で自分の腕　治してるの？
Chain Jail.
カイトを元に戻してよ
This power can only be used on the spiders...
お願いだよ
A power to capture and
restrain the Phantom Troupe.
その後でいいから　ちゃんと…
I've sworn to use this ability
for no other purpose.
なぜ？ 何で　こんなことに？ どうしたんだ？ 何があった　パーム！
I've applied the condition that,
should I use this technique
分からない 私は見るだけで　声は…。 ゴンの様子がおかしいの！
on one who is not a spider,
I will die on the spot.
ピトーが治してるのは カイトじゃなくて自分自身。
A self-imposed restriction. A self-imposed restriction,
and a covenant with myself.
そのそばで ゴンが　へたり込んでるの！
The proof of my resolve.
まさか。
The risk is high.
このコが俺達の手にあれば ピトーは… ピトーは逆らえないはずなのに
But the stronger my resolve, the stronger my Nen!
フフフフ…　ハハハハ…！
Kurapika has captured a member
アハハハ…！
of the Phantom Troupe, his sworn enemies. Armed with resolve and the
willingness to risk his life, an intense battle is about to begin.